<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="es"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://theflyingimagination.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://theflyingimagination.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="es"/><updated>2024-11-02T18:04:48+00:00</updated><id>https://theflyingimagination.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">What’s to come?</title><link href="https://theflyingimagination.github.io/blog/2024/Post_2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What’s to come?"/><published>2024-10-31T14:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-10-31T14:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://theflyingimagination.github.io/blog/2024/Post_2</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://theflyingimagination.github.io/blog/2024/Post_2/"><![CDATA[<p>I finished my bachelors one month ago. I have no pictures yet :camera: :sad:, I have no clue where I will work or how I will integrate the different interests that have a hold on me.</p> <p>I have however a list of things I want to keep learning about</p> <h4 id="the-callers">The Callers</h4> <ul> <li>Languages</li> <ol><li>Portuguese</li> <li>German</li></ol> <li>Law</li> <ol><li>Legaltech</li> <li>Energy and Mining Law</li></ol> <li>Videogames</li> <ol><li>Playing them mostly :happy:</li></ol> <li>Tech</li> <ol><li>Data Analysis</li> <li>Machine Learning</li> <li>Statistics</li> </ol> </ul> <p>Let’s talk only about the first one.</p> <h5 id="languages">Languages</h5> <p>I think my obsession with language will just deepen over time. The wonder of how we are able to make a series of sounds and have other people understand us just astonishes me. At the same time, why would we learn a language today? There are so many tools to eliminate the language barrier. The fact that even though speaking to one another is now easier than ever before, we are still learning languages. Why? I think the most obvious answer is because communication is not the end of the language phenomenon. The meaning of words is not the only horizon of our language experience. Ofcourse meaning matters but the mere fact of speech also trascends the barriers of meaning. Isn’t that what poetry is? Like a cozy trip on a boat of paper over an ending sea of words that describe, dance, change and mutate depending on the reader and the time.</p> <blockquote> <p>Die Heimat| Ihr Wälder meiner Kindheit , wann ich komme, die Ruhe noch einmal wieder?</p> </blockquote> <blockquote> <p>Native Land| O woods of my childhood, when I return, my tranquility again? -F. Hölderlin</p> </blockquote> <p>The other things will have to wait for their own post.</p> <p>See you navigating the words!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="post"/><category term="Philosophy"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am already insane]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Primer Post</title><link href="https://theflyingimagination.github.io/blog/2024/firstpost/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Primer Post"/><published>2024-08-05T19:00:16+00:00</published><updated>2024-08-05T19:00:16+00:00</updated><id>https://theflyingimagination.github.io/blog/2024/firstpost</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://theflyingimagination.github.io/blog/2024/firstpost/"><![CDATA[<p>Hola mundo,</p> <p>En esta primera publicación del blog, quisiera tomarme un momento para reflexionar acerca del uso del blog. ¿Para qué sirve? ¿Para qué quisiera usarlo? A primera vista podría ser cualquiera de estas cosas:</p> <ul> <li>Diario</li> <li>Medio de comunicación</li> <li>Archivo</li> </ul> <p>Quiero usar este espacio para compartir textos, ideas y reflexiones que puedan irse transformando en proyectos, colaboraciones o que simplemente queden como un testimonio de un humano que vivió y que le hizo frente a su existencia. Quiero que este blog sea un espacio de transición entre la vida pública y la vida privada (aunque divisiones no siempre sean tan claras). Mis intereses hacen parte de ese continuo que busco explorar en el blog. Quizá un amigo lo vea en algun momento, quizá un empleador, un servidor público, el público no quiero definirlo previamente. Hay muchas páginas para escribir y compartir contenido muy distinto. Gracias por estar y por leer.</p> <p>El hecho tambien de editar archivos que luego se muestren en una página web, no para de asombrarme. Continuaré aprendiendo acerca de como puedo hacer más con las herramientas presentes e ir poblando el sitio de más vida. Por ahora, si quieres leer más sobre la historia de los blogs mira <a href="https://es.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blog">aqui</a>. Hasta podría utilizarlo como una herramienta para aprender idiomas…las posibilidades son múltiples.</p> <p>terminemos este primer post con alguna cita que pueda sedimentar la voluntad futura</p> <hr/> <blockquote> <p>El orden político es también un orden estético -Armstrong, Isobel</p> </blockquote> <p>El blog o la bitácora hace parte de ambos ordenes e interactuando con el es posible cuestionar o defenderlos. Ojalá el blog, logre este cometido. De cuestionar, transformar, afianzar y proteger los distintos ordenes y sus convergencias.</p> <p>Hasta pronto.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="post"/><category term="bienvenida"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[¿Para qué sirve un blog?]]></summary></entry></feed>